question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The &quot;Berenstein Bears&quot; is the correct spelling of the educational children&#039;s book series&#039; name.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
